okay there we go welcome welcome welcome
everybody welcome to the comma prime
launch all right so first we're gonna
tweet the live stream just find our
hello Prius Prime for the win
hey I gotta figure how to delete the old
stream and I don't know we'll deal with
that later
no we will just share this one let's
check my tweet looks good
yo yo there's no black pandas that's
fake
alright guys I didn't really plan too
much for the live stream I did plan this
is what we're launching it is called
comma Prime and it's a good service it's
also an excuse for you to give us annual
recurring revenue which is something we
need in order to make you know Silicon
Valley are happy with us and they could
they could love us if we just became the
kind of company that makes annual
recurring revenue it's not a credit card
it's not a credit card you know what I'm
just gonna post the medium post and you
guys can all follow along just copy and
paste this let me post on Twitter let's
see the card validator I love you every
Twitter's card validator guys just card
validator space thank you
yeah that looks pretty good ,
I'm launches today exclamation point
dad alright let's make that our pinned
tweet John sorry
Drew's introducing prime okay
so you guys can can link to this and
read it but basically it's got a couple
of cool things one it has an unlimited
data plane meaning you can buy the SIM
card from us and it gives you all the
data you need for you our Eon oh it's
unlimited but it is capped to 512
kilobytes of bandwidth well we could
wait for a few more people to get in
here before we get to the next thing but
you know what we're doing it right like
um you know we're we're a social local
mobile company except if you get rid of
the social so we have mobile and in
order to really be mobile what's more
mobile than being a cell phone provider
I'm so it turns out you can be we're in
NV and oh we didn't come and put towers
in your local neighborhood
we didn't upset your local housing
hallways and stuff we didn't do that we
we partnered unfortunately contractually
I'm not allowed to say who we partnered
with but uh it's they're good they're
good don't worry we didn't partner with
anybody crappy I wouldn't do that to you
guys um so it's unlimited data it will
not work in the UK right now it's us
only we're not sure it might work in
Canada and Mexico but we're gonna say us
only but if you buy one in Canada and
Mexico maybe it will work so we have
some new infrastructure URL out in 0.6
the cue logs the 512 kilobit will allow
you to update load your routes in real
time so they'll show up right away in
the app should be pretty cool
alright so that's the good thing right
that's a good thing um and just so you
will get this out of the way right now
it's $24 a month so you know $24 a month
if you
some old TechCrunch Disrupt Tom had
always been talking about how it's gonna
be $24 a month well guess what now it's
$24 a month um so you can buy it in the
App comic connect but we'll get to all
that in a minute we're gonna talk about
the next perk that you get now this is
kind of the bad one so remember when we
promised unlimited cloud storage well
that was all alive because it turns out
that cloud storage is really expensive
we had free cloud dollars for a while
but the free cloud dollars are running
out so the perks that we can you know
pass on to you are running out too but
basically what this means is you know
you can access all your drives and
Explorer in the app and in Cabana if you
don't have a comma Prime membership you
only get three days one two three but if
you have common crime you get 14 14 days
of unlimited storage
[Music]
you don't like clouds where's your
privacy bro-bro privacy is dead
what we'll get to privacy actually we
have for the next part is pretty private
I like to think that like read privacy
is dead but write privacy can still
definitely exist um so we we these are
expected things these are expected you
should have expected them from us you
know we got a we got to do it just going
discord so we can we can live discord
while we're live youtubing and all the
things so we're gonna go through a few
more things and then we're gonna go
around the office and ask people what
their opinions are on Kama Prime there's
no black panda guys um no no no but we
have one really cool thing for you guys
um that I think oh yeah discord comedy
guy we have one really cool thing for
you guys that I hope I'm you're gonna
appreciate let's see how our how our
tweets are going yeah you know what yeah
okay cool
okay the next thing is the SSH gateway
so this one I'm gonna show you a little
bit one of the first things we built at
kama was a VPN if you own an eon we
should get a free sim if we sign up for
kama prime so the sims are $20 if you
already own an eon if you're buying eon
today or later you get a free sim but
what I think I'm gonna mail you guys all
sims you think I'm really gonna do that
and then me with a little envelope
sitting there forever no no no no it's
not ssh with 22:4 right because we're
not gonna open we're not going to expose
that ssh to the Internet
um you can't really do that right
because you're behind that's what we've
built is an SSH gateway it's not a VPN
um so to be clear what the differences
are we don't like like unlike some other
companies that put all the cars on a VPN
I think they've moved away from that now
but you kind of don't want to do that
right because then all the phones are on
the same VPN so you don't want to do
that sorry if you're in Europe this is
for the America the US people only I'm
not dealing with all your privacy laws
talk to your local representative to
make it easy you know only punish I'm
all for punishing Google and Facebook
but don't don't punish me you know so
it's a gateway meaning what it can do is
know go to discord comma dot ai it
forwards SSH through our servers but
it's end-to-end encrypted meaning we
can't tap into to to any of that stuff
it's your private key and the way that
you enter your private key is you enter
your github username right here so this
is gonna be in zero point six point one
of both Open File intention for plus and
it's gonna grant SSH access to the
public keys that are built into your
Jail we do not have access to your Aeon
no no man in the middle attack if you
guys tell me how to man in the middle
attack this I'll be impressed I thought
about it a bit it seems pretty good our
so our security model is the same as SSH
meaning basically all its real all our
back-end is really doing is exposing the
SSH port on the phone to
yeah it's just like bitcoins encryption
system okay so this is the command
you're gonna use you can go right now to
ssh comma dot i I'm gonna go to it right
here
SSH comma dot I and it shows you how to
set it up so this is the command we have
some scripts to make it easier but if
you want you can just do this this is
the key this is the dongle ID I press
ENTER and give it a minute and boom I'm
connected to the Aeon so this is now
live on any on and you'll be able to
connect your Aeon just as easily um who
wrote that well do you want to go do you
want to go a speaker go up we got to get
to one more thing and then we can go
speak with who wrote the SSH and then we
can answer any questions you might have
about comma Prime so how do you sign up
if you don't have it right now go on
both the iOS and the Android App Store
you can download it's it's it's if you
know what SSH is you can do it um no
it's not Arch Linux Ubuntu servers high
quality um what this does is gives you
remote access to your Eon from anywhere
in the world so if you're a comma Prime
member you can just set up a script on
your computer so you can remotely access
basically your car from anywhere in the
world um we're gonna be rolling out a
lot of features in the coming months
that use like this live integration with
the car
say something hypothetically we could
roll out is like door unlock from the
app or something like that right I don't
know if that's actually gonna happen but
you could theoretically build features
like that for now we're giving you know
are our tools still really are developer
tools so we're giving developers access
remote start yeah SSH right you see not
now you guys are thinking of course you
know yeah remote access to your car it's
your car that you're getting remote
access to know the EON is never offline
for power saving the EON is always
connected to the cell phone network just
like a normal cell phone right but a lot
of the power saving stuff had nothing to
do with the the radio being on in low
power so the comma Prime is available
for purchase in the app for 24 dollars a
month and remote fuel check absolutely
$24 a month it's only available right
now in the
States and if you have an eon currently
you're gonna need a comma sim and you'll
be able to buy that there's a link for
the medium post into comma prime sim for
only oh come on come on you a guy I've
got it cuz it more gotta get some more
tweets on this who's not excited about
comma prime let's just post this on the
discord with out with a nice at channel
yeah we love it at channel you know what
better idea we'll put it in the
announcements channel boom John that's
not what I wanted to do that's at at
this let's just make this the medium
post Oh maybe everyone will click
through that anyway I'll just not not at
it no no no no it'll cancel delete be
okay
I don't even you know when I livestream
normally I have it too you guys can see
my screen you can't even see my screen
right now but let's hope that that
expands nicely so this isn't discord
announcements right here yeah cool sweet
so gamma prime includes the unlimited
cell service we may someday offer a
version that does not know 19 inch
monitors in your cars okay let's go
speak with our app developer Andy who's
done a lot of the work to make comic
prime a possibility hey Andy you want to
talk to the YouTube ease let's go B's
they still scope he's oh yeah we're hang
on a flip the camera so I can
[Music]
and you're really happy about it we're
externalizing the key part of our
infrastructure that we've had for few
years but it's really nice to rewrite it
in a way that we know we can share with
with everyone and it's actually really
nice our old VPN used to kill our car
batteries it would wake up the radio all
the time and we think our new design is
going to be much better on that front so
hopefully less trips to the car
dealership to the Toyota dealership and
in fact the new design uses Athena which
has already been rolled out in open
versions now prime only feature like
common security doing anything oh how
many people had VPNs yeah yeah yeah shut
it down come on Prime
yeah we should do we should do the cheap
prime that doesn't include the data
Sunday - we'll see there's a lot a lot
of Europe a lot of Europe was like is
this only for America yeah yeah we're on
the finances you guys should all buy it
we want lots of annual recurring revenue
cool cool
thanks guys
all right let's take a look at the plant
an interlude for the plant do you want
to say a few words in the scope yeah has
worked hard to make puts the car on the
Internet
like Internet of Things we didn't we
didn't say Internet of Things nearly
enough in our medium post I'm gonna edit
the categories right now
Mykel watts I'm glad you like it Willem
deep anything oh good
yeah no it's uh this has been a long
time in the making we can't mention we
didn't mention him yeah I think so Joe
I think yeah I think this is really
important to the future of the company
you know making sure we can provide the
best possible service no matter where
you are and not make you have to go home
and connect to Wi-Fi yeah cool thanks
yeah
well a deep and quick comments yes
they're very excited about at the plant
özil he's a nice plant guys Harold do
you have any comments about common prime
[Laughter]
is it coming to the UK I don't know if
there's enough demand you know what if
there's enough demand somehow you can
signal that demand to me we can work
hard to try to find a UK partner what
did I know there whose name what's my
scam well if we just want the
connectivity know so the SSH feature
only works if you're a comma Prime
member and we're gonna start doing this
with a lot more of the sort of
cloud-based features basically the cloud
costs us money and unless it makes money
we cannot afford the cloud so if you
want the cloud to continue by kava prior
summary the announcement check out the
medium post on Twitter well you pay 20
so you pass 24 you'll have a better
experience you know well really maybe
maybe we'll do we'll do some we'll do
some special colors for people on disk
or who have comma Prime let's see how
many SIM cards we sold let's see if we
sold a lot of SIM cards he's come from a
popular product let's find out LTE band
compatibility don't worry about that
all the Aeons are very compatible with
the comma Prime Network alright alright
how many have we sold so far zero no no
no I'm kidding he's sold one we sold uh
I bet on you guys I bet on you guys to
buy lots of SIM cards go to the shop
right now buy a SIM card before we run
out no if you sign up the
cards not free - SIM cards $20 it's only
free for the people who buy eons from
now on we did sell one yawn though so
maybe comma Prime is sold in neon you
guys we really need to we need to sell
things cuz that's what we do as a
company and you guys need to buy things
I think I think that's how it works you
see all these eons look back to you
running out like that used to be full of
eons and like now it's not full of eons
anymore now it's full of like phones and
boxes
you just bought thank you thank you we
are we are gonna be the Android smart
cars um so yeah sign up today thank you
thank you for it age thank you come on
get in here buy them buy them buy them
we're not selling any large monitors for
the cars no that's not happening
no you can't buy them with comma points
unfortunately wait wait you guys bought
I don't see your orders on here no
what's going on
guys you got to click the Buy button you
got to click the checkout button all the
way you can't just add it to the cart
that doesn't make us any money of how
many users yeah
while the live stream tweet got very
little got very little traction so we're
just gonna delete that
bye-bye tweet and hopefully people will
be excited about comma crime just bought
just bought shout out shout out to to
Christian who's working on me hybrid
Corolla did you actually buy let me
check yes I see your purchase right here
excellent thank you thank you please by
Colin prime guys we're not getting
interviewed by anybody we're just
rolling out the products it really is a
great product it makes you eat a lot
better it's $20 for the SIM card and
then $24 per month you know it's it's
it's a it's a good deal you should buy
comma Prime if you're in Indonesia don't
buy the SIM card it will not work for
you is it a data
it's an unlimited data service what even
is phone mean today oh your violin I
think GT mobile cyclones that make sense
yeah no it's very reasonable you can
also tether you know you can your Yan
can serve as a hotspot you can tether
you can connect other devices through
this it's unlimited some limits you guys
can use all the data you want if the
price rises in the future will you be
grandfathered in perhaps we can
certainly work out things like that
especially as we start to add some real
perks to come a crime this is just the
beginning
no I'm not selling a stop asking for the
big monitor we're not doing any big
monitors
what is it check out the medium post I'm
gonna link the medium post right here in
the YouTube comments
just go to all you want I can find it
from Twitter but I deleted the live
stream post so that's too bad yeah you
guys can post attack are nice we're not
using arch linux stop with the monitor I
have to figure out how to delete this
one
this shouldn't be a thing edit video
[Music]
how do I do we I don't know okay all
right that's that's that's mostly what
we're talking about today for comm prime
any yeah phone sourcing we're good we're
running on Windows nah we're running on
Linux everything here is on Linux let me
just get a link to the medium post that
I can post right here in the YouTube
perfect
well you can certainly do both yeah
updates but OTA updates you know I know
it's for I think a car is like a an
internet-connected device now it really
is an internet-connected device would
call a crime cool IOT that's right all
I'm gonna I was gonna change the I was
gonna change the things on the medium
post to include the Internet of Things
story tag this is a way to problem cool
guys thank you for joining today's live
stream that was today's project
announcement comma prime it's available
at shop comma dot a I can the uplink
handle and how long will it take well so
we've moved to a we've moved to a cue
lanks which mean we upload a really
small amount of data that describes your
route pretty well and that can keep up
in real time that's about a hundred K
per second so at 512 bandwidth should
keep it up no problem um does it work in
Canada maybe it may work in Canada in
Mexico
we're not sure yet if you try it then
let us know how it works and if it works
well then we'll advertise that it works
in Canada and Mexico as well it's a good
way to it's a good way to get an
unlimited data plan it it shows if you
guys buy it it shows that there's demand
for these features and then we'll put
more effort into developing even more
features like you know like we're
talking before about the remote door
unlocks Road engine start we can do
things also like comment security say
somebody caps on the hood of your car
can send you a ping your text phone
right if come on if al cam can exist as
a company doing only this and we can
roll it out with an OTA update so I'm
talking about cool dog - I'm super happy
I love when people buy things at shop
comedy I
yes sentry mode we call it comma
security right yes sentry mode his
security right is that the feature you
I want well let's see how many people
buy it no it can't cure your depression
this isn't that kind of AD the truth is
no product is gonna have any influence
on your happiness it just might make
your life a little bit better and a
little bit more convenient
yes entry mode right no remote drive
remote AC perhaps I mean this is all
open source stuff right so you'll be
able once you get in to add whatever you
want to your your open pilot or shipper
plus vote with your credit card I like
that I like that this is gonna be a 30
minute livestream so we got four more
minutes to go does it do where's my park
stolen car absolutely that's already
live today in the comic Connect app I'm
sorry your card got declined that sounds
like something you need to take up with
your bank
yeah live stream capability that's the
kind of stuff that can be rolled out
look if I look at the bills if I look at
the bills and I'm like man we're making
30 grand a month annual recurring
revenue on common prime then I'm very
interested in writing all those features
for you because let's see actually know
what if we can get up to ten grand a
month recurring revenue I can hire a
full-time developer to write features
for you also comma connect app you know
make sure we're gonna be aggressive
about fixing all bugs yeah you can track
other people using your car absolutely
please use it at eclis but that's not my
problem we just write software Todd
starts the car to cool off yeah it turns
on the AC can the panteon read obd codes
for check engine lights of course it can
but you got to write the software you'll
code for food well you know what I'll do
one better just um submit pull requests
to explore in Cabana making them fast
and perform and I'll be very happy with
you is SSH open source of course it is
it's called OpenSSH check neo ask the
operating system distribution we have
tells you what version it is you can
find every line of the code in there
which cars will get priority you know
which cars get priority Hondas and
Toyotas thirty dollars shipping to
Canada yeah I mean that's the
International shipping charge I don't
know what to tell you why don't you
order
- while you're at it - thank you thank
you Ethan
each table um I can't read YouTube's
comments or nowhere near as good as
periscopes comments but their stream
quality is just so much better
you bought kama prime congratulations
thank you for buying kama prime you are
making it possible for us to develop
features for everybody everybody else
because the money from Kabul prime will
go straight into kama prime features
let's see how many how many comic lines
you sold oh oh we got we got we're up
200 we got actually a lot
oh they're rolling in now we got five we
got five thank you all very much
we got five we got one Aeon if you could
keep the Aeon in your car 24/7 so we
keep our eons in the car 24/7 I
understand that in some places maybe the
temperature doesn't allow this but I
think if you park it out of the Sun it's
gonna be fine no matter what we've made
great strides in the amount of power the
Aeon uses so shouldn't kill your car
battery unless you leave your car for
over a week so that's pretty good comma
crime uses like really no more battery
in San Diego you've killed two we have
all our cars with the Aeons in them
Texas yeah if you leave it in the Sun
yeah don't leave your cars in the Sun
that's not good for your cars anyway
batteries the batteries good um so we we
leave the Aeons used to kill our car in
a weekend but we did a lot to lower
power consumption we've removed OpenVPN
off of our phones and now the battery
life is more than a week so you should
be pretty good you can make a tinfoil
you can make a sunshade I mean people
have those for their cars too for a
reason you know it's good to keep your
whole car cool um battery list Eon with
USB power over the comma power the
batteries less of a big deal than you
guys think we moved to San Diego a
couple of months ago life's a lot better
down here as that's a scam
yeah any last questions about comma
Prime now it processed cool are you
telling me we have one more order you
two
no I can't I delete it off Twitter it's
just a spur private YouTube Jim yeah I
tried to look and I couldn't see it yeah
yeah yeah it's kind of the medium post
on Twitter YouTube thought some people
find it turns out these don't convert
that one medium positive media post
convert very well yes we've started to
track analytics because we're gonna be a
real company and uh where is your one
you don't like your lane curves show you
the executive bathroom all right yeah
we'll go to the bathroom you go to the
bathroom on stream oh this is the comi i
stream if it was my twitch we could do
that no oh what science oh yeah okay I
don't want to know about that let's see
how many let's see how many how many
things we are sold do we sell a lot I
would show you guys this screen but it
has everybody's names on it so we're not
gonna do that
hey privacy great again I mean I don't
want access to your device because it's
just a liability for me oh my god shows
so many we've sold eight we've sold
eight all right should we keep the
stream going until I can't count how
many we've sold on my fingers oh this is
pretty good guys
I bet hi we have an internal like office
little betting pool to see how many are
gonna be sold
I bet thirty-two so you guys don't let
me down come on everyone by comment
Prime today's the day to buy it you'll
get that SIM card in the mail you're
gonna love it
we got eight so far let's just get three
more let's keep the stream going until
we get three more buys I'll check this
out guys look at how much common prime
we have in stock
four-twenty so you only need to buy 24
more no no no he's gonna sell 11 we've
sold it so far they're pretty good it
was a little bit slow at first but I'm
glad you guys are coming around to see
all the benefits of that , prime can
offer you the sim cards only $20 to get
started I'm not signing anybody's comic
Prime we're not doing that walks are
what's kama Prime check out the medium
post kama prime is our new $24 a month
unlimited data service it's not just
unlimited data it provides more than
four times as much cloud storage as as
the newly nerfed cloud storage without
comma Prime it provides SSH to remotely
access your Aeon in a very secure way
such that we do not have access to your
Aeon only you with your private key no
you can't you have to get a comma sim
which is the SIM cards that we sell
how many aeons sold last month a bit
over 100 is this we're not actually
allowed to say contractually the name of
who said mobile network partner provider
might be but it is a good one and if you
you know think a little bit maybe you
can you can you guys can solve the
mystery
Thanks walks or no that's a weird
question Al's dee sign some of the sims
to sell them faster known and I don't
know we're not doing any of that no it's
not Verizon it's a mystery but it's a
good one don't worry it's not like
sprint or 18 to you or anything like
that all right we got we got us out
we're still at 8 guys was still at 8 no
come on I'm not signing them now maybe
maybe we'll just leave you today maybe
we'll just leave you today I'm not
licking any other sim stop that guys oh
man right now we're starting to get some
reach on Twitter much better
transform more than three gigs a month I
think if you do it and do that math
again she'll be able to do quite a bit
more you just just bought one high
refresh it again oh oh it just flows
another one that's nine guys that's nine
that's mine kama primes no we don't have
any marketing people we have me who does
live streams occasionally we don't
really do that we do so we have we have
a great designer and like we design
sales right sales are designed they're
not marketed yeah
we are real yeah it's a level in three
gigs and there's they're actually no cap
you can upload as much as you want make
sure that I don't think it ever I don't
think it throttles you we've tried
I don't think it's one point three
terabytes either I think that's
aggressive as well I think I think when
you do the math it's somewhere in like
the thirty gigabyte range let me let me
let me do the math out sorry I can't
sorry I can't show you this dream this
screen but I just don't have a good way
to do it but okay so it's 512 kilobits
per second times 60 that's per minute
times 60 knots per hour times 24 times
30 and that is of course kilobits not
kill a byte so we're gonna divide that
by a illness they kill a bit yellow by
doing data bytes
so if I did the math right it's that all
right so it's it's 512 kilobyte 60
minutes 60 60 seconds per minute 60
minutes per hour 24 hours per day 30
days per month divided by 8 because it's
bytes not pets kilobytes equals hundred
twenty hundred thirty sixty five
gigabytes so that's theoretically
possible but you get you get less than
that right but like really you don't
need that much
um kanikama prime Simba used as a
hotspot not in an eon no they only work
with eons ah ok google' yeah yeah yeah
dance listen did it the better way than
uh than I did um yeah that Tara was was
those you're not going we're not going
terror big here
he owns use about I think I think it's
about like no contract cancel anytime
it's month-to-month $24 no roaming
charges as far as I know we definitely
won't charge you more than $24 a month
the Eon can be used as a hotspot my face
is red so hot in here
let's see how many more sales we have we
have sales sales I love your sales only
nine I'm pretty happy with knowing guys
ma'am maps are never gonna happen maps
are a dumb idea I'm getting to why maps
her dumb idea on some other live stream
may consider signing up the inside PR
gets merged we should merge the inside
PR change the is a yeah I'm happy with
nine guys nine is pretty good the sales
are gonna trickle in all day thank you
all for watching this official comma
prime launch party that's a pretty good
deal Oh
gonna order one now all wait I'm gonna
hang on if you're gonna order one now
I'm gonna hang on we'll get to ten zero
six one goes live later today I think to
beta and then ya know maps are stupid
you know what I will show you guys
something cool I will show you guys
something cool
since all 113 of you stuck with me um
through this live stream but actually
only if we buy more stuff you gotta buy
more stuff yes
look here see the red light see the
green light
see how when it's red it's like slow
down see you when it's green it's like
go ahead yeah so secret Maps is dead
what's the point of a grey panda um so
if you have a grey pandit your data is
included in the training set uh so it'll
work better in your area um most likely
good then there's no black panda can be
on autopilot work in France maybe is the
stuff you do learn in a research
upstream almost we're working on it oh
oh you're gonna buy one too are we
actually gonna get to eleven I'm so
happy when we get to the number I say
we're gonna get to gonna buy a new car
soon so hold on if you do buy a neon
today by the way the SIM card is
included for free I did tell you all
that eons were appreciating assets we
didn't get to ten yet we're still at
nine I did tell you all that eons are
appreciating assets so future eons are
gonna include a free free free Kyle
prime sim card just for you guys we got
it we got to get it we gotta get I feel
like we can do it guys I feel like we
could do it you buy a panda while you're
at it - you don't want just buy more
stuff I mean the store is open for
everything guys come to the beautiful
comma a I store it's open for everything
you're number ten all right all right
let's let's refresh this and see if this
guy's actually telling the truth grd no
no no we don't have any beanies anymore
those just sold out
oh yeah Jared D is telling the truth he
really did buy us in we have one two
three four five six seven eight nine
ten can we get to 11 can we get to 11
who else wants to buy a sim you won't
regret it you'll love your new , Prime
get out your wallets guys it's 20 bucks
but don't buy it if you're not gonna use
it save the common crimes him two people
who are gonna use it
oh hold up Bob camac is buying oh yeah
you're gonna be number 11 that's cool
I'm super happy when we get to I don't
have any more traffic light detection
that's the only one I have not merely
have one common insurance maybe
eventually right yeah the affiliate
program it didn't it didn't increase
sales
that's who cancelled it wouldn't try
other things like that maybe in the
future it is only for the u.s. I'm sorry
I'm sorry I wish our partner had more I
can't even know how much I could say I
wish they were all everywhere they might
be in Canada in Mexico we don't really
know I'm looking up coverage map of
unnamed provider perfect oh yeah oh is
that 11 is that 11 did you just buy 11
just go no no no we're still 10 just got
in what did you missed you that I the
video contest was a good deal we could
do the video contest again and I'll
spend more time judging it I feel like I
was too quick on the last time judging
the video contest yeah we don't do live
streams that often only now you missed
everything
oh I'm holding up for one more person is
gonna get it what was the video contest
thousand bucks who can make the best
Oakland pilot video yeah I think it does
work in Mexico and Canada show you
something fun in the office I will go to
data center uh-oh my mom just texted me
I'm going back to Jersey tomorrow I'm
using Ubuntu 1604 if you do the video
contest no I don't know about Iran
alright guys welcome to the hello in the
data center
cool
this is where the models get trained
have you wondered why the models have
gotten so good lately
it's because the data is so big got some
cars in here
the Prius Corolla it's all the way back
there
Oh Michael Watts ordered Michael Watts
ordered oh this is exciting yeah we have
zi8 40s for everybody at the office
that guy was telling the truth I don't
know if you want me to say your name
publically I forget if your name is in
your username we don't out anybody we
care deeply about some kinds of privacy
so yeah there's that we just reached 11
sales guys I'm so happy that you guys
could get me to 11 you're all incredible
scope ease and I want you to go out
every day and remember all Brad's buying
right now all we're gonna get to 12 well
that's even more than 11 that's crazy
that's crazy that's so many sales I'm
super happy that you guys are buying
these because every comic Prime
subscription that we sell increases the
likelihood that we're gonna hire a
full-time developer to write come prime
features review I'm sorry I have to go
we reached 11 we reached 11 but I'm glad
we made it there you guys got a 45
minute stream we have to we had to get
through those last few sales but since
we made it that's all I have to say
today only $24 a month $20 for the sim
included free with all new eons you'll
be able to activate , prime directly
from your comic connect app available
for iOS and Android the comic connect
app is free if you have a neon already
download it you're gonna have a great
time it's got a lot of five-star reviews
let's keep it that way if you have
something bad to say tell us we'll fix
it and leave us a good review thank you
very much bye bye bye bye bye bye bye
YouTube nice coppice bye